Adam Pedley Software Engineer

adampedley01@gmail.com • 07764524658 Keighley, WRY, UK

> github.com/adampedleydev linkedin.com/in/adam-pedley www.adampedlev.dev

Experienced web developer with a strong background in front-end development and a passion for creating user-friendly, visually appealing websites. Skilled in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with experience building responsive websites using modern frameworks such as React and Angular.

SKILLS

Programming: TypeScript, JavaScript, Node.js, React, GraphQL, React Native, Python.

Database: PostgreSQL, Redis, MySQL.

DevOps: AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Terraform.

Other: Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, WebStorm, IntelliJ, Linux, Jira/

EXPERIENCE

Extension Plans UK
Web Developer / I.T Manager

November 2021 - Present

Aided one of the leading architectural practices in the UK in revamping and taking lead on new implementations of both internal and customer-facing web applications & services. Worked with a plethora of technologies to design and develop a bespoke customer portal, internal automation and task delegation systems. Has also designed and developed several websites for sister companies.

Freelance, Nationwide Web Developer

April 2016 – November 2021

Plan and develop web applications for customers, coordinating with them to complete projects within a strict time frame. Deliver impeccable support to companies' C-Level heads in updating their web-based marketing strategies. Evaluate and resolve issues regarding clients, projects, and general business using appropriate course of action. Interface with multiple large and small clients across foundations and local charities by serving as contractor. Foster lucrative relations with colleagues.

- Managed large amounts of data and assured all databases and websites comply with the highest standard of security prior to shipping.
- Cultivated sound rapport with local businesses which led to huge referred work.

2nd Time Around, Keighley | 3 Hutchison, Keighley Sales Assistant

July 2015 - April 2016

Achieved and met sales objectives by coordinating with the team. Promptly addressed customers' queries, issues, and questions in a busy high-street store. Established contracts between organisation and customers as well as carried out credit checks via company software. Expertly performed management functions including locking up / cashing up.

- Provided excellent customer service, improved client's satisfaction and retention level, accomplished organisational objectives, and satisfied client's needs.
- Consistently met 100%+ of independent sales goals on a weekly basis.

EDUCATION

Bachelor (Honours) in Music

The Open University, 2021

8+ A*-C Grade GCSE's including Mathematics & English

Holy Family Catholic School, 2015